Guide to the David H. H. Felix Papers, 1929-1946
David H. H. Felix papers Register 1929-1946
Felix, David H. H.
1200 Items 1.6 Linear Feet
Duke University. David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Durham, North Carolina 27708-0185
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Felix, David H. H.
International Conference of the Labour and Socialist International (1933: Paris, France).
Philadelphia (Pa.)--Politics and government
Socialist Party (U.S.).--Pennsylvania
Contents of Collection
- Correspondence
  - Radio Speeches, Debating the News, WPEN, 1929-1940 (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1935-1942
- Subject Files
  - International Conference of the Labour and Socialist International, Paris, 1933
  - Socialist Party, Campaign Committee, 1940, May-Dec., (2 folders)
  - Socialist Party, National Executive Committee, File No. 54457, 1940, Feb.-1946
  - Socialist Party, National Executive Committee, File No. 54458, 1940, May-1942, Apr.
  - Socialist Party, National Executive Committee, File No. 54458, 1942, May-1944, Nov. (Box 2)
  - Socialist Party, National Executive Committee, File No. 54459, 1940, Dec.-1944, (4 folders)
  - Socialist Party, National Executive Committee, File No. 54460, 1940, May-Aug.
  - Socialist Party, National Executive Committee, File No. 54460, 1940, Sept.-Oct. (Box 3)
- Writings and Speeches
  - Minutes: National Executive Committee, Special National Convention, 1937, undated
  - Radio Speeches, Debating the News, WPEN, 1931-1942, undated, (3 folders)
  - Miscellaneous speeches, undated
  - Miscellaneous writings, undated (Box 4)
- Miscellaneous
  - Printed Material: Proceedings. International Conference of the Labour and Socialist International, Paris, 1933, Aug. 21-25
  - Pictures: International Conference of the Labour and Socialist International, Paris, 1933, Aug. 21-25
- Oversize Materials
  - International Conference of the Labour and Socialist International, Paris, 1933 (Oversize-box 21)